primalforce.net 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy

#### Disclaimer:

This applies to the use of any savings code, when available, at checkout to receive the advertised discount. The special offers are web-only and expire at the time of expiration. Free shipping where indicated. International orders will incur additional shipping & handling charges.  Discounts do not be apply to future Auto Delivery orders unless otherwise stated. Savings codes are not permitted for use on previous orders but are available during limited times.

#### Dr. Sears’ Privacy Policy

Dr. Sears recognizes the importance of protecting your personal information and your trust in us. Therefore, we take the responsibility of handling your personal information extremely seriously.

#### Your E-mail Address

When you subscribe to any of our e-mail newsletters, your address is added to our database. We’ll use your address to send you our newsletters. We may also use your address to help you complete a checkout you abandoned or forgot about. We will not sell, rent, or in any other way share your e-mail address with anyone.

You can remove your address from our mailing list by following the instructions at the end of every e-mail we send.

#### Personal Information

Our staff will never ask you for personal information, such as your credit card number, except when you’re placing an order. At that time, we’ll require only the information needed to complete and fulfill your order.

We will never ask for information that’s not needed to complete your order.

#### Confidentiality

Any correspondence you send to us, including e-mail, is considered confidential unless you tell us otherwise. We will not add your name to our e-mail list without your permission. We won’t quote you in our issues, on the web sites, or in promotional materials without your consent.

If you contact us to inquire about an order, our customer service staff will ask you to verify your identity by confirming information already in your record.

#### Your Mailing Address

When you give us your mailing address, we will use this information to fulfill your order and to send you information on other products you might find interesting. If you don’t want us to send you this other information, please contact our customer service department:

Customer Service  
11905 Southern Blvd.  
Royal Palm Beach, FL 33411

Or you can email us using our [online contact form](http://primalforce.net/contact.php) or call us toll-free at 1.866.895.8555.

#### Cookies

Cookies are tiny files placed on your computer by web sites you visit. They can be used to make your next visit to that site more convenient (by remembering settings, for example).

Our web sites use cookies only to track how many people visit each page, how long they stay, and that sort of statistical data. We don’t store or collect any personal information with cookies.

*** These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease.**

**Disclaimer:** The information and recommendations provided on this website have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration and are for educational purposes only. The products offered on this site are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease. You should always ask your doctor before using any products.

Al Sears, M.D., is a practicing physician with extensive experience in the fields of complementary and natural healthcare. The recommendation and materials on this site represent his opinion based on his years of practicing medicine. Any recommendations are not intended to replace the advice of your physician. You are encouraged to seek advice from a competent medical professional regarding the applicability of any recommendations with regard to your symptoms or condition. It is important that you do not reduce, change or discontinue any medication or treatment without consulting your physician first.
